Contact

gergelovakarla@aol.com

www.linkedin.com/in/karla-gergelov %C3%A1-05728346 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Foreign Languages Archtics Opera

Languages

Czech (Native or Bilingual)
French (Native or Bilingual)
Russian (Elementary)

Karla Gergelová

Développeur Web et Mobile à la recherche d'un stage dès le 19 février 2020

Strasbourg Area, France

Summary

Je suis actuellement développeur en formation chez Webforce3 et je suis à la recherche d'un stage pour me permettre de compléter ma formation et d'obtenir un titre professionnel développeur web et mobile (BAC+2).

After working in the hospitality industry for about 5years, while playing basketball on a professional and semi-professional level, I have decided that I would like to find out how all those different systems that we used in the industry were actually utilized on the backend.

I always loved learning and picking up new systems which is why I got interested in software programming.

I love to challenge myself and utilize my brain in a different capacity.

Experience

WebForce3
Fulltime Student
October 2019 - Present (5 months)
Strasbourg Area, France

ACSL Basketball Furdenheim Semi-professional Basketball Player August 2018 - Present (1 year 7 months)

Furdenheim, Alsace, France

National league féminin 2 in 2018-2019 and National league féminin 1 in 2019-2020 in Furdenheim.

La Société Protectrice des Animaux (SPA)
Volunteer
August 2018 - Present (1 year 7 months)
Strasbourg Area, France

Dog walking

Pigier

Education Administrator September 2018 - May 2019 (9 months)

Strasbourg Area, France

Education Administrator (Assistante Pédagogique) at Pigier Création.

IKEA Group

Customer Service Representative October 2017 - August 2018 (11 months)

Reims, Champagne-Ardenne, France

Soissons Cuffies Aisne Basketball Semi-Professional Basketball Player September 2016 - June 2018 (1 year 10 months)

Soissons, Picardy, France

National league féminin 2 in 2016-2017 and National league féminin 3 in 2017-2018

L'Assiette Champenoise Hotel Receptionist and Concierge January 2017 - October 2017 (10 months)

Tinqueux, Champagne-Ardenne, France

http://www.assiettechampenoise.com

Hotel La Villa Eugene Assistant General Manager March 2016 - November 2016 (9 months) Épernay, Champagne-Ardenne, France

http://www.villa-eugene.com/en/accueil/

Reims Basket Feminin Professional Basketball Player August 2015 - June 2016 (11 months)

Reims Area, France

Playing basketball in French LF2 league.

http://www.reimsbasketfeminin.fr/

UBCUA Basketball club

Professional basketball player August 2014 - June 2015 (11 months)

Alençon, Lower Normandy, France

Playing basketball in French NF2 league.

www.ubcua.com

La Société Protectrice des Animaux (SPA) Volunteer September 2013 - June 2014 (10 months)

Strasbourg Area, France

-volunteer as a dog walker and also helped answer visitors questions http://www.spa-strasbourg.org/index.php

ACSL Basketball Furdenheim Professional Basketball Player August 2013 - June 2014 (11 months) Strasbourg Area, France

Playing basketball in French NF2 league.

www.fufubasket.org

BK Lokomotiva Karlovy Vary Professional Basketball player August 2012 - May 2013 (10 months) District Karlovy Vary, Czech Republic

Played basketball for a team in the best Czech basketball League=ZBL

www.bklokomotiva.cz

The Animal Foundation Volunteer August 2011 - June 2012 (11 months) Las Vegas, Nevada

volunteer as a dog walker and also helped answer visitors questions

MGM Resorts International
Management Associate in Hotel Operations
2011 - 2012 (1 year)
Las Vegas, Nevada

MAP at Monte Carlo Resort and Casino

- -Front desk rotation-worked day, swing, grave shifts as a front desk clerk and in addition worked together with a supervisor and assistant hotel manager at Monte Carlo Resort and Casino
- -Shadowed and worked in Human Resources, Security, Safety and Engineering, VIP Services, Group reservations, PBX, Concierge, Valet, Bell Desk, Spa, Housekeeping, EVS, Food and Beverage, Special Events and Entertainment at Monte Carlo

Bellagio

UNLV Hotel College Mentor Program September 2010 - August 2011 (1 year)

Las Vegas, Nevada

- -Mentored by Diana Hewitt, Director of Pit Clerk Operations at Bellagio, who i learnt from about the casino side of the industry
- -Shadowed managers at different departments within the property, such as Front Desk, Marketing, Special Events, Title 31, Surveillance and Sensi Restaurant

Enterprise Rent-A-Car Management Internship program May 2010 - August 2010 (4 months)

Las Vegas, Nevada

- -Performed office duties: made reservations, dealt with phone calls
- -Obtained different sales techniques related to Enterprise extra products
- -Utilized adaptive learning strategy to provide excellent customer service

Drogerie Central Sales Associate May 2008 - August 2008 (4 months)

Zlin, Czech Republic

- -Assisted customers with products while providing excellent customer service
- -Handled exchange of money between diverse guests and company in a fastpaced environment

Drogerie Central Sales Associate May 2004 - August 2004 (4 months)

Zlin, Czech Republic

-Assisted customers with products while providing excellent customer service

-Handled exchange of money between diverse guests and company in a fastpaced environment

Education

WebForce3

Bac +2 Développeur web et mobile · (2019 - 2020)

University of Nevada-Las Vegas

Bachelor of Science in Hotel Administration, Hospitality

Management · (2007 - 2011)